Marc Brown Papers MS148
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Postcards from Buster audiovisual material, 1998 -- 2007; 2004; MS148.004; 133 Audiovisual Object(s)
  - Sample reel, 2003-10-10; MS148.004.651.00001 (Box 651)
  - Sample reel, 2003-10-10; MS148.004.652.00001; WGBH (Firm) (Box 652)
  - Sample reel, 2003-10-10; MS148.004.653.00001; WGBH (Firm) (Box 653)
  - Sample reel, 2004; MS148.004.654.00001; WGBH (Firm); Marc Brown Studios (Box 654)
    TRT: 4:30.
  - Sample reel, 2004; MS148.004.655.00001; WGBH (Firm); Marc Brown Studios (Box 655)
  - Sample reel, 2004; MS148.004.656.00001; WGBH (Firm); Marc Brown Studios (Box 656)
  - Sample reel, 2004; MS148.004.657.00001; WGBH (Firm); Marc Brown Studios (Box 657)
  - Location title examples, 2004-09-22; MS148.004.658.00001; Cookie Jar Entertainment (Box 658)
    Ch1: full stereo mix left, ch2: full stereo mix right.
  - Postcards from Buster, Episode #39 Roswell, 2004-08-09; MS148.004.659.00001; WGBH (Firm) (Box 659)
    First draft. Associated mix for approval can be found at MS148/004-671#00001. Associated tapes can be found at MS148/004-642#00001. Associated client copy can be found at MS148/004-643#00001.
  - Postcards from Buster, Episode #012, swimming in the desert, 2004-09-15; MS148.004.660.00001; Cookie Jar Entertainment (Box 660)
    VHS NTSC, TCBI, Mix for approval. Associated production files can be found at MS148/003-024#00058-00059. Associated drafts can be found at MS148/004-566#00001 and MS148/004-567#00001.
  - Postcards from Buster, Episode #012, hoops and drums, 2004-09-15; MS148.004.661.00001; Cookie Jar Entertainment (Box 661)
    VHS NTSC, TCBI, Mix for approval. Associated production files can be found at MS148/003-024#00056-00057. Associated drafts can be found at MS148/004-564#00001 and MS148/004-565#00001. Associated tape can be found at MS148/004-647#00001.
  - Postcards from Buster, Episode #40 Seattle #1, gospel, 2004-08-04; MS148.004.662.00001; Cookie Jar Entertainment (Box 662)
    First draft. No associated production files. Associated tapes can be found at MS148/004-645#00001. Associated client copy can be found at MS148/004-644#00001.